{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
    {
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Who%20is%20the%20villain%20company%20in%20%22Stardew%20Valley%22%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Joja%20Co%20",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "Ronin",
    "Empire",
    "Robotnik%20Industry%27s%20"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "General%20Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What%20is%20on%20display%20in%20the%20Madame%20Tussaud%27s%20museum%20in%20London%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Wax%20sculptures",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "Designer%20clothing",
    "Unreleased%20film%20reels",
    "Vintage%20cars"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Vehicles",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which%20car%20is%20the%20first%20mass-produced%20hybrid%20vehicle%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Toyota%20Prius",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "Chevrolet%20Volt",
    "Honda%20Fit",
    "Peugeot%20308%20R%20HYbrid"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The%20human%20right%20lung%20has%20how%20many%20lobes%3F",
    "correct_answer": "3",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "4",
    "2",
    "1"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Books",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The%20book%20%22The%20Little%20Prince%22%20was%20written%20by...",
    "correct_answer": "Antoine%20de%20Saint-Exup%C3%A9ry",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "Miguel%20de%20Cervantes%20Saavedra",
    "Jane%20Austen",
    "F.%20Scott%20Fitzgerald"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In%20%22Call%20Of%20Duty%3A%20Zombies%22%2C%20which%20weapon%20does%20NOT%20deal%20any%20damage%3F",
    "correct_answer": "31-79%20JGb215",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "Sliquifier",
    "V-R11",
    "Wunderwaffe%20DG-2"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The%20Khajiit%20are%20a%20race%20of%20cat-like%20creatures%20from%20which%20epic%20series%20of%20role-playing%20games%2C%20set%20across%20the%20land%20of%20Tamriel%3F",
    "correct_answer": "The%20Elder%20Scrolls",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "Lord%20of%20the%20Rings",
    "The%20Witcher",
    "Neverwinter%20Nights"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Animals",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20of%20the%20Common%20Chimpanzee%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Pan%20troglodytes",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "Gorilla%20gorilla",
    "Pan%20paniscus",
    "Panthera%20leo"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "General%20Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "The%20word%20%22aprosexia%22%20means%20which%20of%20the%20following%3F",
    "correct_answer": "The%20inability%20to%20concentrate%20on%20anything",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "The%20inability%20to%20make%20decisions",
    "A%20feverish%20desire%20to%20rip%20one%27s%20clothes%20off",
    "The%20inability%20to%20stand%20up"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What%20animal%20did%20Queen%20Pasipahe%20sleep%20with%20before%20she%20gave%20birth%20to%20the%20Minotaur%20in%20Greek%20Mythology%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Bull",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "Pig",
    "Ox",
    "Horse"
    ]
    }
    ]
    }